One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Why did the video cut out?!
Show us Marineford!
Hurry and show it already!
Something must have happened to their Visual Transponder Snails, there's nothing we can do!
The Navy and Whitebeard made a deal? Can it be true?!
Show us something!
Did Whitebeard really sell out his companions?!
What's going on in this war?!
What will happen to the world?!
What an annoying move by the Navy...
I guess the show's over, huh?
We sailed back here just so we could watch the war...
now they're having trouble with the Visual Transponder Snails?
There's no way that's the truth.
Huh? It's not?
You sure are an idiot. It's obvious that they're hiding something.
Something they don't want pirates, or anyone else, to see...
Captain Bonney...
Shut up! Leave me alone!
Whitebeard sold out his companions?
Like hell. He's a legend because he never does anything like that.
Assault
Time to set sail, Bepo.
Aye aye, Captain!
Come with me, Jean Bart!
That's right. It doesn't look like it'll be fixed anytime soon.
Right now, there's no way to tell what's happening in Marineford.
Meteor Volcano!
We're not letting you escape!
Melt the ice and take away their footing!
T-The water...
It's hot!
The magma is making the water boil!
Get out of the water, quickly!
Hey, look!
This way is blocked too!
Is there nothing we can do against this wall?!
Whitebeard...
T-The Pops's attacks aren't working... That's no ordinary wall!
Now, it's time to end this.
The Moby Dick took a direct hit from the magma!
Put out the fire!
Hurry!
You have to hold on!
Don't let the ship sink!
We're gonna travel the seas with our friends, and Ace, once more!
Whitebeard. Your era is at an end!
The Moby Dick...
Damn it! Damn the Navy!
That was our pride and joy!
Damn! They destroyed our ship! The ship that's carried the Whitebeard Pirates for decades!
Forgive me.
We're losing our only way into the plaza!
The plan is progressing smoothly.
The execution of Portgas D. Ace... will proceed...
immediately!
We can't even see what's going on!
There's no way we'll let them kill Ace!
Yeah...
There's still one way...
One single path...
The path that Oars made for us!
If we go that way, we'll be killed. The Navy is sure to be waiting for us.
This is no time to stand around and chat!
Yeah... If we're gonna save Ace, that's the only way...
Ace!
Straw Hat...
We'll go, too!
Yeah!
That route is far too obvious!
It's not over yet! Hold them off as best as you can!
Fire!
There's no way the enemy would ignore the only opening!
It's definitely a trap!
Fire!
Straw Hat-boy!
Luffy-kun!
Little Oars Jr.! He was still alive?!
Ace... kun...
Oars...
I'm... gonna protect... Ace-kun...
Oars!
Captain Squard!
You guys...
Right!
Are you alright, Luffy-kun?
Really, how reckless can vyou get?
Prepare to fire.
Shoot!
Oars!
I've gotta do something...
I've gotta hurry...
They're gonna execute Ace!
Yes, we must act quickly!
Jinbe!
I've got...
a favor to ask!
You sure are persistent...
He's already half-dead! Finish him off!
Oh, don't bother. I'll do it.
Kizaru-san!
We need to get the execution over with, and fast.
At times like this, it's best to just pierce them right through the head...
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
Lu-
Luffy!
Oh, my. You finally made it here.
Quite an entrance, son of Dragon.
This youngster sure is scary...
Ace's little brother just went straight over the wall!
That kid...
If nothing else, I praise your tenacity.
But you're not ready for this stage yet.
There's no way you can beat us, you know?
Give Ace...
back!
He's just as reckless as his brother.
Oars! Stay where you are.
We'll need your strength.
Pops...
Jozu! Time for our trump card!
Sure!
All men, prepare yourselves!
We're breaking into the plaza!
Rubber-Rubber...
Stamp Gatling!
Gear Second!
I don't have time to fight these guys!
How cunning of him.
Too slow.
On my mark!
Yes sir!
Do it!
Ace!!
Who was that?!
Bastard!
Considering your old grudge against Whitebeard, I had thought we were lucky...
Crocodile!
Him!
Huh... it wasn't my turn yet?
You were hell-bent on killing the Pops.
What's this sudden change of heart?
That dying old man?
I'll eliminate him later.
But right now...
I don't want to see you enjoying victory!
Hey now, Crocodile-man!
D-Doflamingo!
So you're ditching me to team up with Whitebeard?
It's enough to make a guy jealous, ya know...
I don't team up with anybody.
That's the same as brushing me off.
More or less.
I don't get what's going on... but we were saved.
End of the line, Straw Hat!
Die!
Get out of...
my way!
Stop right there, Straw Hat!
I will not let you go any further!
Move it!
Shave!
Moon Walk!
Iron Body...
Smash!
Rubber-Rubber...
Iron Body!
Bullet!
Stop Straw Hat!
Don't let him get any closer!
Admiral Sakazuki!
That hurts!
Damn it!
I'm indebted to your granddad, but...
I have no choice!
You have chosen your own death!
You! Do not lay a hand on Luffy!
Admiral!
That's...
The Commander of the First Division... Marco!
Thanks for saving me.
Don't mention it.
Three people have penetrated the plaza!
Devil Fruit users are passing over the walls!
Cross the water and head for Oars!
Whatever happens, get to the plaza!
The pirates are getting desperate.
Defend the gap in the walls!
Yes sir!
Even after losing their ships and their footing, they're still as frenzied as ever.
Foolish pirates.
They're sitting ducks! Fire!
Everyone, get on board!
Yeah!
Hold on tight!
No way! A ship...
Big trouble!
Another coated ship has emerged from the bay!
Damn it!
It was hiding underwater the whole time!
I don't remember saying that we'd used all of our ships!
It's a paddle ship!
It's going to ram us!
What?!
Sink it! Just like the Moby Dick!
No, not the ship!
Shoot Oars!
Huh? Oars?
Too late!
Here we go, everyone!
H-He pulled the whole ship in!
The intruders have breached the walls!
We're in the plaza!
Let's save Ace!
Time to overthrow Navy HQ!
Hang in there, Ace!
They got us.
There was one tiny mouse hole in the walls, and they swarmed right in.
Those walls may wind up working against us.
Pops!
Whitebeard...
Still got your head, Ace?
We made it!
Now Ace-kun can be resc-
Oars!
Save... Ace-kun...
Oars...
Whitebeard has entered the plaza!
Stand back, my sons.
Men!
Rescue Ace, and destroy the Navy!
Garp...
Yeah.
It looks like even we have to take a hand in this!
Editing, Sewil
QC, Galaxy 9000, Pepperjack
Karaoke, KaitouYahiko
Timing, Halee
Soundtracking, Halee
Translation, Yibis
Raws, Crunchyroll